question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "&quot;Resident Evil 7&quot; is the first first-person Resident Evil game.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Bulbasaur is the only starter pokemon that is a Grass\/Poison type.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Rollercoaster Tycoon 1 and 2 were developed by Chris Sawyer.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Tony Hawk&#039;s extreme sports videogames revolve around performing professional BMX tricks.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Ana was added as a new hero for the game Overwatch on July 19th, 2016.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Activision created Battlefield 1.", "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "&quot;Undertale&quot; is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is refered to as &quot;The Shape&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Nintendo&#039;s Luigi was originally just called Green Mario?",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
   ]
